[sighs]
You know what we should all do?
Go see a musical.
Sure.
You know which one
we should see?
The 1996 Tony Award winner.
Do you happen to know
the name of that one?
I don't know, um, "Grease?"
No.
"Rent?"
Yes! "Rent!"
Okay, so when do you want to go?
What? Oh, I'm sorry.
I can't, I'm busy.
- Hey.
- 'Hey.'
Man, it is so hard
to shop for girls.
Oh!
Yes, it is, at Office Max!
What did you get her?
A pen.
It's two gifts in one.
It's a pen that's also a clock.
Huh?
[laughs]
You can't give her that.
- Why not?
- Because she's not 11!
And it's not the seventh night
of Chanukah!
Okay, honey,
what he means by that is..
Well, this is a very nice gift
maybe it's just not something
a boyfriend gives.
Sure it is.
She needs a pen for work.
She's writing,
she turns it over.
Whoa! It's time
for my date with Joey!
Alright, look, look. What..
What did you get
for Angela Del Veccio
for her birthday?
She didn't have a birthday
while we were going out.
For three years?
Look, it's too late,
and I got an audition.
I can't shop anymore. I..
Alright, I will go out
and I will try
to find something for her, okay?
Thanks, man.
And oh, while you're at it
could you get her a card?
Would you like me to write her
a little poem as well?
Or just get a card
that has a poem already in it.